## **DAMJAN PJEVIĆ**

damjan.pjevic@gmail.com

+386 40 933 622

www.pjevic.com

linkedin.com/in/damjan-pjevic/

Ambitious, reliable and open-minded individual with a great passion in tech and business. With a Bachelors in Multimedia Engineering focused in Digital Communication and a history in the computer software industry, I am in pursuit of my master's degree in business informatics at the Economics Faculty of Ljubljana. Experienced in working with the users, public speaking and working in a team and showed a history of working in the fields of programming, telecommunications, event organisation, digital media, social media and marketing.

## **SKILLS**

IT: Website management, Mobile application development, Basics in telecommunications.

Basics in marketing and PR: Content creation, Managing social media, Verbal communication, Promotions

Other: event organisation, working in a team, working under pressure, communication skills

Programming: Java, JavaScript, C#, Python, Processing, HTML, CSS, SQL, Android Studio, Unity, WordPress.

Languages: Slovenian C2, English C2, Serbian B2, German B1, Russian A1.

Multiple years of experience in Adobe Creative Cloud, Office Suite.

European driving license - AM, B, B1 (since 2014), International driving licence.

## **EXPERIENCES**

2019 –	Website manager at <b>Value Add Games</b> : Updating and maintaining the website and the online shop (using WordPress, WooCommerce). Helped with their most successful marketing campaign.
2019	Programmer at <b>Jozef Stefan Institute</b> , Department of Intelligent Systems – Using Python and basics in auto-encoders worked on a project that builds on Sandberg's paper - Dissolving the Fermi Paradox.
2019	Took part in the <i>BEST Summer Course</i> in Wroclaw, Poland that focuses on company management and how technology and good marketing strategy can embrace its success.
2017	Selected as one of the top 20 out of 350 global teams in OnePlus Student Marketing Challenge.
2016 – 2019	Took part in various promotional events of the Faculty of Electrical Engineering.
2016 – 2019	<b>LMMFE Video Team</b> – Broadcasting/Technical assistant at a couple of events in cooperation with RTV SLO.
2016	Regional winners in global competition <i>OSCE Peer to Peer: Challenging Extremism</i> by a successfully developed and pitched tool for challenging violent extremism.
2015 – 2016	International Student Organisation EESTEC - LC Ljubljana.
	- As one of the Coordinators, successfully managed the PR group for <i>EESTEC Competition for Android</i> 2015 and reached out to more students than any year before.
	- Took part in a week-long seminar in Istanbul, Turkey focused on Marketing and Multimedia.
2015 – 2019	Selected Class Projects:
	- Extension of the Pan-European Mobile Emergency Application with extended reality (Thesis project)
	- Using Android SDK created and designed a translation app for one of the Slovene dialects.
2011 – 2015	High School Debate club.
	<ul> <li>Took part in three different YouthPass Exchanges all focused on international Peer-to-Peer communication.</li> </ul>

## **EDUCATION**

2020 – 2022	Business Informatics – Master's.
	School of Economics and Business, University of Ljubljana, Slovenia
2015 – 2019	Multimedia Engineering – Bachelor's. Average grade: 9.0
	Faculty of Electrical Engineering, University of Ljubljana, Slovenia
	Hochschule für Kunst Bremen, Germany (Erasmus Exchange 2017)